# Ralph Anthony A. de Luna

# Supervisor

- O Block 4 Lot 18 Phase 2C, Brgy. Cotcot, Lilioan, Cebu
- **9** +63 (915) 259 3599
- ralph.deluna.rtatzs@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ralph-anthony-de-luna-73a91a16a/



I spent five years maintaining a Quality Assurance System of an ISO-certified client that produces electronics for Aviation. I am well acquainted with the manufacturing environment from onsite deployments. My recent work involves the development of software for the Internet of Things (IoT) which includes reading data from sensors and controlling field devices. I am eager to learn and can work with less supervision. You can expect me to have initiative.

#### **Education:**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science
April 2010 – April 2015

University of San Carlos – Sitio Nasipit, Talamban, Cebu City, Philippines

## **Work History:**

Supervisor

January 2020 – Present N-PAX Cebu Corporation, Mandaue City, Cebu

Senior Programmer

January 2018 – December 2019 N-PAX Cebu Corporation, Mandaue City, Cebu

Programmer

November 2015 – January 2018 N-PAX Cebu Corporation, Mandaue City, Cebu

#### Skills:

- Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Systems Development Life Cycle Waterfall Model
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- WinForms Development in C#
- Database Administration using MSSQL
- Mobile Development Android in Java
- Visual Studio Team Foundations Server (Repository)
- Git Repository (GitHub)
- Windows Communication Foundation Services (Web API)
- Windows Server Hyper-V (Virtual Servers)
- Keyence Programmable Logic Controller (Ladder Programming IoT)
- Arduino C++ (IoT)
- Modbus RTU RS485 (Sensors & Field devices IoT)
- Unity3D in C# (Sensor & Plant device simulations)

#### **Character References:**

#### Kirstine Mae Enriquez

ERP Supervisor

N-PAX Cebu Corporation

Phone: +63 (998) 594 9609

#### Peter Eugene Aroy

**B-P Supervisor** 

N-PAX Philippines Inc.

Phone: +63 (915) 748 0481

### Hubert Eamiguel

Software Developer Analyst

Accenture

Phone: +63 (998) 594 9610